麦克斯 有什么两字的词代表"快乐"
Max, what's a five-letter word for "happy"?
答案不是我的第一任妻子"海伦"
And it's not my first wife, Helen.
我本来要说"喝醉"
I was gonna suggest "Drunk."
因为我就醉着
Maybe 'cause I am.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
猜猜我的大衣底下有什么
Guess what I have under my coat.
绝对不是上次的冰激凌圣代
And it's not ice cream sundaes like last time.
这次是我的孕肚
It's my baby bump!
苏菲 你开始显孕态了
Aw, Sophie, you're showing!
而且这次"显"的不是你的奶头
And this time, it's not either of your nipples.
看 才四个月大
Ah, look! Only four months.
我就快跟卡戴珊一样了
And I'm already approaching Kardashian.
这可是医生说的
And that's quoting the doctor.
太厉害了
Impressive.
你里面可能东南西北都怀上了
You may have a North, South, East, and West in there.
这宝宝可会踢了
The baby really kicks.
以后估计会是个足球员
So it's either gonna be a soccer player
不然就是洛杉矶的暴力警察
or a Los Angeles policeman.
阿憨 你觉得
Hey, Han, what do you think
我的孕肚 孕肚 孕肚肚如何啊
of my baby bump, baby bump, baby bump?
在我的国家 我们从来不评论两件事
In my country, we never comment on two things:
女人的孕事跟金正恩的新发型
women's pregnancies or Kim Jong-un's haircut.
金枪鱼麦芽酒
One tuna malt.
我写的是金枪鱼三明治
That was a tuna melt.
麦克斯 阿憨要来了
Max, here comes Han.
记得 我们得对他加倍好
Now remember, we have to be extra nice
才能得到他对我们的甜品吧大力支持
so we can get his support for our new dessert bar.
他哪有办法支持我们
How can he support us?
他的脖子都要"支持"不住自己的大头了
He can barely support his giant head.
像这样的句子
See, that's the kind of stuff
就是你等会最好别说的句子
you're gonna have to stay away from.
这是演哪出
What's this about?
上次你们对我笑
Last time you were smiling,
我差点失去了一只耳朵
I almost lost an ear.
我好莱坞的款项终于到账了
Well, my Hollywood money has finally arrived,
阿憨 你也知道 我和麦克斯
and as you know, Han, Max and I want to
想把小蛋糕窗口转型为甜品吧
convert the cupcake window into a dessert bar.
而你也知道 我想把你俩转型为服务员
And as you know, I want to convert you two into waitresses.
别这样 阿憨 这完全不会影响到餐厅
Come on, Han, it won't affect the diner at all.
我们只是想借用一下洗碗盘间
All we want to do is use the dish room--
三种原生大肠杆菌中其中两种的发源地
home of two of the three original strands of E. Coli.
我拒绝
It's a no.
我的心理医生说今年我得
My therapist said this had to be the year
为自己站出来 以及少喝汽水
of standing up for myself and cutting out soda.
行啊 那你站起来吧
All right, well go ahead, stand up.
但我十分乐意看到你们俩去祸害别人
But because I would like to see you make someone else miserable,
所以我能介绍个房产中介
I know a real estate agent
能帮忙你们找到新店面
that could help you two find a new space.
你说的是房产中介还是中国
Did you say "Real estate Asian"?
她的名字叫依薇 我在教会认识的
Her name is Evie, and I know her from my church.
只能说她对我的腰下悬挂之物
And let's just say she's been angling
垂涎已久 使出各种套路
for what I've got dangling.
你的钥匙吗
Your keys?
智障 她喜欢我好吗
She likes me, you shrews!
好吧 我们对他好就是这下场
Okay, well that's what we get for being nice.
继续说甜品吧
So back to the dessert bar,
你有收到我发给你 很酷的凳子图吗
did you get the pictures I sent you of those cool stools?
我看到信件主旨是"很酷的凳子[大便]"
I saw the subject heading was "Cool stools,"
我还以为你连我们最后一点底限都打破了
and I thought you finally shattered our last boundary.
把你的手机给我
Here, give me your phone.
我找不到凳子图了
I can't find the stools.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我真没想到会看到这个
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
狗狗开车的图吗
Is it that dog driving?
不是 是你的手机里为什么
No, why do you still have a picture
还存有你前男友的照片
of your ex-boyfriend on your phone?
你居然左右滑乱看我的照片
You swiped on my phone?
万一里面有羞羞的照片怎么办
What if I had something embarrassing in there?
比如我娇艳欲滴的"鲍"照
Like a tasteful hoo-ha shot?
为什么你手机里还有兰迪的照片
Why do you still have a picture of Randy on your phone?
这个示意心理医生跟你分手的洛城男
The guy who broke up with you in L.A. using a therapist?
这表现出了藕断丝连之情
This bespeaks of an unresolved longing.
"婊"砸最好"表"说话了
Be-stop be-talking right now.
我有打算要删掉的 只是还没空删而已
I am gonna delete them, I just haven't gotten around to it yet.
比如我也没空对别人好
Like being nice to people.
天啊 这也太邪门了
Oh, my God, this is too weird.
-怎么了 -是兰迪
-What? -It's Randy.
麦克斯是在这工作吗
Does Max work here?
这里闻起来像她形容的那样
This smells like the place she described.
我每天上班都是靠这味儿来导航的
That smell's how I find my way to work every day.
他来这里干嘛 我不想见到他
What is he doing here? I don't want to see him.
那就别转头 因为他就在你身后
Then don't turn around, 'cause he's right behind you.
麦克斯
Max?
很高兴再见到你
Good to see you.
你不准备转过身来吗
You're not gonna turn around?
不了
No, I'm good.
你不愿意为这男人转身吗
You're not gonna turn around for that guy?
我是你 我就为他"转弯"了
I mean, I would turn around for that guy.
看到公告上你们有特餐
See on the board you have some specials.
那我就点一份碎牛"喃"三明治
I guess I'll have the sloppy...job?
是"腩"
It's "Joe."
有时候我的"月"写得像"口"字旁
Sometimes my "E"S look like "B"s.
显然以后写公告特餐这事 还是我来吧
Clearly, I need to start writing the specials on the board.
这样吧 我就点一个肉"现"卷
You know what, just give me the meat...load?
可悲的是 还真是"现"而不是肉"馅"
That one, sadly, is spelled right.
兰迪 你来这里干嘛
Randy, what are you doing here?
律师工作 这周末来这出差
Lawyer stuff. I'm in town for the weekend.
我的传奇歌手委托人要告女神卡卡
My client, Tony Bennett, is suing Lady Gaga
害他变得不酷炫
for making him uncool.
然后顺路过来看看麦克斯想不想见我
And I thought I'd come by and see if Max wanted to see me.
我也不介意来喝一杯热"卡卡"
I guess I also wouldn't mind a cup of hot caca.
麦克斯 你真的不转身吗
Max... you're not gonna turn around?
好吧 那我走了
Okay. Guess I better go.
再见
Well, bye.
Bye.
我靠
Damn it!
又被卡通史酷比狗的假脚步声招数骗了
Fell for the ol' Scooby Doo fake footsteps.
-你好吗 -好极了
-How are you? -I'm great.
从来没这么好过
Never been greater.
麦克斯 我需要人去清理
Max, I need someone to clean up
女厕里的婴儿换尿布区
the baby-changing station in the ladies' room.
-我们没这区域 -现在有了
-We don't have one. -We do now.
那我就不打扰你工作了
I guess I better let you get back to work.
如果你愿意见我 就打给我
If you want to see me, give me a call.
托尼下午三点半就吃完晚饭睡觉了
Tony has dinner and goes to bed around 3:30.
兰迪觉得他就这么带着他的帅脸
Randy thinks he can just show up with his face
好身材 外加精壮不显粗的脖子
and his body and his muscular-but-not-too-thick neck
来我面前 我就会忘了他甩掉我的事吗
and think I'm gonna forget that he dumped me?
麦克斯 别说"甩"
Max, don't say "dumped."
要说"散伙" 比较没这么狠
Say "kicked to the curb." It's kinder.
麦克斯 我们有个没人管的可疑包裹问题呢
Oh, Max, we have an unattended package situation.
跟刚才无人管的露鸟[包裹]流浪汉简直一样
Not unlike that homeless guy we just passed on the stoop.
我好久没看到这么大的盒子[阴户]了
Wow, that's the biggest box I've seen
上次还是意外点开《大胖美女》黄片的时候呢
since I accidentally clicked on a "big, beautiful women" porn.
所以的"意外"不会是
It stops being an "accident"
你扯着嗓子把我叫醒
when you wake me up by yelling,
说"快来看这部大胖美女的黄片"
"Hey, check out this 'big, beautiful women' porn!"
这好刺激啊
Well, this is exciting.
我好久没有惊喜包裹[产子]了
I haven't had a surprise delivery
上次我原以为是吃辣拉稀呢
since that baby I felt was just Chipolte.
还吃辣呢[墨西哥菜]
Chipolte.
麦克斯 你刚说的不是真的吧
Max, that never really happened, right?
亲爱的 你喜欢哪个答案就信哪个
Whatever makes you sleep sounder, sweetheart.
那就是不是真的
Never happened.
天啊 是三合一口味爆米花
Oh, good God! It's three kinds of popcorn!
还有十成十的失望
And all kinds of disappointment.
疯狂吧
Crazy?
有经典黄油味
You've got your standard butter,
甜滋滋的焦糖口味
you got your sweet, sweet caramel,
以及最后这不需任何介绍的爆米花口味
and finally, the popcorn that needs no introduction,
起司
cheese!
我的起司神啊 太好吃啦
Cheese-us, that's good.
是兰迪送的
It's from Randy.
"这么做"爆"老套 但我很想你
"I know it's corny, but I miss you.
爱你的兰迪"
Love, Randy."
我去 他还很会写情书吗
Oh, great, so he's a great writer too?
我为什么生他气来着
Why am I mad at him again?
好了 他很明显知道你的弱点就是
All right, he obviously knows your sweet spot
连锁药店的食品杂货
is the grocery aisle at Rite Aid,
但我不能再次让垃圾食品影响你的判断力
but I am not gonna let junk food cloud your judgment again.
就像上次你为了拿巧克力碎饼干而去捐血
Like that time you donated blood for a chocolate chip cookie.
我还喝到了柳橙汁好吗
Hey, I also got orange juice.
安安 姑娘们
Hey, girls.
麦克斯 你的东西寄错寄到楼上去了
Max, this was delivered upstairs for you.
抱歉上面有咬痕
Uh, sorry about the bite marks,
但我的宝宝闻到了味道就说
but the baby a whiff of the pimento loaf and said,
"我一定得来一口"
"Oh, I just got to have it."
"我知道我是个"腊"圾
"I know I was a jerky,
让我用意大利腊肠向你赔罪"
so let me say sorry with salami."
怎么 兰迪是手下有一帮段子手
What, does Randy have, like, a team of writers
在帮他写这些双关语情书吗
working on these things?
兰迪吗
Randy?
你是说那个脖子精壮的帅哥吗
You mean that hot guy with the muscular neck?
精壮又不显粗
Muscular, but not too thick.
对啊
Yeah!
他想用意大利腊肠与脆饼
He's trying to win you back with salamis
来重获你的芳心吗
and delicious biscotti?
里面没看到有脆饼啊
There's no biscotti in here.
这个嘛...
Oh, yeah, well...
宝宝说想吃点甜的
the baby needed something sweet.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh.
宝宝踢了我
The baby just kicked.
我好开心啊
Oh, that brings me so much joy.
他又踢了
It did it again!
天啊
My gosh.
他好像是在跟着腊肠动
Hey, I think it's following the salami!
谢谢你今天带我们来看店面 依薇
Thank you so much for showing us the space today, Evie.
我确定麦克斯很快就到了
I'm sure Max will be here any minute.
很难让她准时出席
It's hard for her to be on time.
或保持清醒一小时以上
Or sober for more than an hour.
这里的优点就是地点跟价格
Well, the pros are the location and the price.
而我猜缺点大概就是这里死过的十一个人
And the cons are the 11 people I'm guessing have died in here.
这里的确有些小 但人们喜欢小东西啊
It is a little small, but people like small.
我知道自己特喜欢
I know I do.
而我特想知道这里的自然光怎么样
And I know I am very curious about the natural light in here.
我也可以把任何人事物变美
And I can make anything pretty.
问我高中的一字眉印度同学就知道
Just ask Suda Mahmoosh from high school.
她本来绰号"一眉师太"
Everyone called her Bert
后来是我用镊子让她"眉开"眼笑
till I worked my tweezer magic.
你们得立马决定 因为有另外三个
Well, you have to act now, because there are three other
非常有吸引力的竞标者
very attractive offers on the table.
而其中一个想带我去坐游轮呢
And one wants to take me on a cruise.
我怎么告诉你的
What did I tell you?
她用眼神把我的衣服一件件扒掉
She's undressing me with her eyes.
我用我的眼神帮你把衣服一件件穿上
Well, I'm buttoning you back up with mine.
我得去接个电话
Oh, I have to take this.
对了 阿憨
And Han?
她刚才用韩文跟你说的什么呀
What did she say to you in Korean?
她对追求你 可是干劲十足啊
'Cause she was coming at you hard.
她想要我对她"干"劲十足
That she wants me to come at her hard.
那到底哪里不好呢 阿憨
Well, what's the problem, Han?
她外表可人 又很喜欢你
I mean, she's cute and she likes you,
而且你也没资格问为何
and it's not your job to ask why.
这问题应该是我跟麦克斯来问
That's mine and Max's.
问题就是她来自一个很保守的家庭
The problem is that she's from a very conservative family,
她想要保持处子之身直到结婚
and she wants to be a virgin when she gets married.
双处婚姻
A two-virgin marriage.
多有爱啊
That's cute.
还是太像了反而不好
Or is it too matchy-matchy?
不不 她想要在婚前滚床单
No, no, she wants to have sex before marriage.
我迷糊了 她想保持处子之身
I'm confused-- she wants be a virgin,
可是又想跟你滚床单吗
but she wants to have sex?
所以是"除了那里哪都行"的意思
Like an "everything but" situation.
可以这么说
So to speak.
但她找到绕过"前庭"的漏洞 这漏洞也带"庭"字
She's found a loophole, and it rhymes with loophole.
什么
What?
她腰部以下基本就像是会所
Below the waist, she's like a mullet--
前庭做门面 后庭开派对
business in the front, party in the back.
-还没懂吗 -我懂了
-Still nothing? -Yeah, I got it!
我只是不想讨论这事
I just don't want to talk about it.
这种事情你应该跟一个男人讨论
This is a conversation you need to have with a man.
所以等麦克斯哥来了
And when Max gets here,
我敢肯定她会先取笑你
I'm sure she'll make fun of you
然后教你怎么做
and then tell you what to do.
抱歉 卡洛琳 这店面刚租掉了
I'm sorry, Caroline. The space just got rented.
这附近的店面通常不会闲置太久
Spaces don't stay empty for long around here.
阿憨 你可以陪我去车那里吗
Han, can you walk me to my car?
帮我把"东西"放进我的"后"车箱
I need help putting something in my trunk.
随"后"跟"上"
I'm right behind you!
我不是那个意思
I mean...
小小米奇和米妮要去哪里呀
Where are Mickey and Minnie Mouse going?
麦克斯 你去哪儿了
Max, where were you?
你来晚了 这店面没了
You're late, we lost the space,
我还不幸得知 我们的中介
and I had to learn that our real estate agent
想跟阿憨上床 但又想保持
wants to have sex with Han, but remain a...
处子之"前"身
front virgin.
请理解宝宝的苦
Please understand me.
她想钻前半身处子的漏洞吗
Oh, she's working the ol' loophole argument?
怎么 你从没听说过吗
What, you never heard of that?
圣布里奇特学校的女学生发明的啊
The girls at St. Bridget's invented it.
我受不了了
I can't take any more of this!
她们也是这么说
That's what they said!
但后来又"受得住"了
But then they did.
你不是该从"后门"进来吗
Shouldn't you be coming in through the back door?
不得不说 麦克斯 我超意外
I got to say, Max, I'm really surprised
你没有心软跑去见兰迪
you didn't cave in and see Randy.
模特是瘦骨嶙嶙 你是铁骨铮铮
You're showing more backbone than a supermodel.
是啊 我才不会见兰迪呢
Yup, I'm not gonna see Randy!
我绝对不会见兰迪
I'm not seeing Randy at all!
好啦 别人还说我讲话大声呢
Okay, and they say I'm the loud one.
出去 卡洛琳
Get out of here, Caroline!
我在跟你说话呢
Who I am talking to.
你能去外面
Uh, can you go outside
给我带回点外面的东西吗
and bring me something from outside?
-比如什么 -我不知道
- Like what? - Oh, I don't know.
康尼岛的纪念品
A souvenir from Coney Island.
曼哈顿老太太的帽子
An old woman's hat from Manhattan.
好吧 外面的东西 懂了
Okay, sure. Outside stuff, got it.
谢啦 不用着急回来哈
Thanks. Take your time.
你怎么还在这里
What are you still doing here?
你说你洗个澡就走了
You said you were just gonna take as shower and leave.
我在等水变热啊
I was waiting for the water to get hot.
等了足足四个小时
Took four hours!
你得在卡洛琳回来之前走
You have to go before Caroline gets back.
我好久没偷偷溜出一间公寓了
Wow, I haven't snuck out of an apartment
上一次还是帮我朋友逃出科学神教
since I helped my friend escape Scientology.
她回来了 你们俩被抓奸了
Well, she's back. And you two are busted.
我就知道他在这儿
I knew he was in here.
我刚在沙发上玩自拍
I saw his 12-pack in my phone
从手机里看见了他的12块腹肌
when I was taking a couch selfie.
你居然还让他用我浴巾
And you let him use my towel?
那还是我的床单 兼夏日婚礼的裙子
It's also my sheet/dress for summer weddings.
好 这样吧
Okay, you know what?
我去脱掉你的裙子
I'm gonna get out of your dress
顺便给你俩一分钟时间
and give you two a minute.
真不敢相信你又跟兰迪睡了
I can't believe you had sex with Randy.
不止是"睡"了哦
More than just sex!
别插嘴
Stay out of this!
你说你会好好考虑
You said you were gonna mull it over.
权衡利弊
Weigh the pros and cons.
在你来之前
You know, before you came here,
我都是跟职业罪犯[利]和骗子[弊]在一起
I used to date pros and cons.
我不擅长思考事情
I'm not used to thinking about stuff
然后做出合理的判断
and making sound judgments.
我去年才知道原来药瓶上还有说明
I just found out last year there are instructions on medicine.
抱歉我希望你能得到最好的
Well, I'm sorry if I want what's best for you.
我插个嘴 说件事
Just throwing this out there--
我有一份很棒的工作 一栋很好的房子
got a great job, nice house,
自98年起我就是美国汽车协会的资深老司机
full-fledged AAA member since 1998.
请别插嘴 这是我和麦克斯之间的事
Please, this is between me and Max.
我们得想清楚你们俩该怎么办
We have to figure out what to do about you two.
我是喜欢他 但我不想再次受到伤害
Well, I-I like him, but I don't want to get hurt again.
瞧 这就是利弊
See? Those are pros and cons.
这真让人兴奋
This is exciting.
外面是什么情况
What's going on out there?
听起来我好像在接受审判
'Cause it kind of sounds like I'm on trial.
算了 这是一个重要的决定
You know what? This is a big decision.
或许我们该睡一觉 明天再决定
Maybe we should all just sleep on it.
不就是因为"睡"才让我现在惹了一身骚吗
Isn't sleeping on it what got me in trouble in the first place?
我想到了兰迪的另一个优点
I thought of another pro for Randy.
前后看他都是爷们 不会前后不一
He looks like a man from the front and from the back.
当今年代很少见了哟
Very rare in these times.
好 我会把这点记到表上
Okay, I'll put it on the list.
不 这是我活下去的理由表
Oh, no, this is my list of reasons to stay alive.
我该告诉你 上面只剩一个理由了
You should know I'm down to one.
依薇想带你俩去看看布鲁克林的一个小地方
Evie found a small place in Brooklyn she wants you to see.
她也想我去看她的"小地方"
As for the small place she wants me to see,
但我还没决定
I haven't decided.
卡洛琳 我们来讨论一下
Caroline, let's get some pros and cons going
憨姥姥游"后庭"的利弊吧
for Han taking the A-train.
这是你离阴道最近的一次亲密接触
I mean, this is the closest to a vagina
我们从来没想过你会有此等机会
that any of us ever thought you'd be.
那么如果我决定不上呢
So if I decide to pass,
你们会小看我吗
you won't think less of me?
阿憨 你已经小到不能再小了
Han, that would be impossible.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
如果你怀孕了 地铁上会有人给你让座呢
You know, you get a seat on the subway if you're pregnant
只要你愿意坐到老人的大腿上
and willing to sit on an old person's lap.
苏菲 想一个7个字母的词 算了
Sophie, what's a seven-letter word for--oh, hell.
估计你想出答案得三年 太久了 不值当
Three years is too long to spend on one crossword.
在我妈看来
According to my mom,
念三年级也很浪费时间 不值当
it's too long to spend in third grade too.
小卡 来我卡座
Carol, come to my booth.
我的宝宝好像又踢我了
I think my baby's gonna kick again.
苏菲 我们在工作呢
Uh, Sophie, we're kind of working.
你居然有工作啊
Oh, you got a job?
你好
Hey, there.
我来找麦克斯
I'm, uh, here for Max.
还有第14个词是
Oh, and 14 across?
木瓜
Papaya.
靠 老子又重燃希望了
Damn! I'm back in!
兰迪 我们还没商量出决定呢
Randy, we actually haven't come to a decision yet.
我想上庭
Well, I want my day in court.
我的名额送你 已经是第三次要上庭了
Oh, you could have mine. It's the third.
你们都知道 我是一名律师
As you know, I'm a lawyer.
通常我不会在一个
And I usually don't practice in a courtroom
供应猪"牌"的法庭实战
that serves something called pork chip.
但如果我要在这里接受审判
But if I'm gonna be on trial here,
那我要为自己辩护
I'm gonna make my case.
好吧 但我要说...
Okay, but let me just say--
你需要我的利弊表吗
Do you want the list of pros and cons?
不用 我能行
I got this.
我需要确定我能放心再把
I need to make sure that I can trust you
我闺蜜的真心交给你
with my best friend's heart again.
天啊 这活脱就是《傲骨贤妻》啊
Oh, my God, that was pure Good Wife.
麦克斯 去苏菲的卡座坐着
Max, go have a seat in Sophie's booth.
没事 但我想来些猪"牌"
That's fine, but I'm getting some of that pork chip.
味道不错 宝贝
It's good, baby.
这道菜还会配有土豆"泥巴"
It comes with a side of ass potatoes.
兰迪
Randy.
你住在洛杉矶 麦克斯住在纽约
You live in L.A. Max lives in New York.
你有没有说过
Did you or did you not say you're bad
你不擅长谈异地恋
at long-distance relationships?
说过
I did.
你有没有说过
And did you or did you not say
你只是来这里待个周末
that you're just in town for the weekend?
这话我的确说过
Well, I did say that--
女士 你有没有看见
Ma'am, do you or do you not see me
我在进行模拟审判呢
conducting a mock trial up in here?
兰迪 你有没有
Randy, did you or did you not
示意一名心理医生来跟麦克斯分手 因为...
break up with Max using a therapist because...
你自己说不出口
you couldn't do it yourself?
-我... -回答我的问题
-Well, I-- -Answer the question!
有
Yes.
卡洛琳 你好牛逼
Caroline, girl, you are good.
当年我因为身为黑人
Where were you when I got arrested
在华盛顿州被捕时 你在哪里
for being black in Tacoma?
你住在洛杉矶 麦克斯住在纽约
You're living in L.A., Max is living in New York,
你们俩都在否认现实
and you're both living in denial
明明这段感情就无法维持
if you think a relationship can work.
我能走近卡座 为自己辩护吗
May I approach the booth and mount my defense?
你昨天进行了三次"高潮"水平的辩护
You mounted the defense three times yesterday.
反对 亲吻证人
Objection! Kissing the witness!
你们在外面搞什么鬼啊
What the hell is going on out here?
他们在审判这个白人版的比利·迪·威廉姆斯
They are putting that white Billy Dee Williams on trial.
你说的没错 我的确伤害了她
You're right, I did hurt her.
示意心理医生跟她提分手 是一个错误的决定
Breaking up with her using a therapist was a bad decision.
跟她分手 本身就是一个错误的决定
Breaking up with her at all was a bad decision.
她为什么要相信我 如果我只是
And why should she trust me if I'm just gonna
来这里待个周末就走了呢
blow into town for the weekend and leave?
你作为一个律师
Well, for a lawyer,
论点貌似是在给自己挖坑跳啊
you're not making a great case for yourself.
对啊
Yeah.
如果我是你的话
I mean, if I were you,
我会立马脱掉我的上衣
I'd just take my shirt off right now.
而真相是
And the truth is...
我不是来这里出差
I'm not here on business.
托尼·班尼特没有告女神卡卡
Tony Bennett isn't suing Lady Gaga.
尽管他该告 但不关我事
Although he should. I'm just not involved.
我这周末来纽约
I came to New York for the weekend
是为了见麦克斯
to see Max.
她也是我要留在纽约
And she's the reason I'm gonna stay
整整一个月的原因
in New York for a month
看看这段感情能不能够继续
to see if we can make this work.
我觉得那算是两个加分点
I think that should count as two pros.
你真的会为我留在这里吗
You're really gonna stay here for me?
我总是情不自禁想你
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
我甚至没有删掉手机里你的照片
I didn't even delete your photos off my phone.
你也太丢人了吧
Well, that's pathetic.
我找到了超适合你们甜点吧的地方
So I think I found the perfect space for your dessert bar.
肯定比你之前带我们去看的那"地洞"好吧
It's got to be better than the other holes you showed us.
它处于威廉斯堡最潮的地方
Well, it's in the trendiest part of Williamsburg,
租金便宜 房东是一个非常好的人
cheap, and the landlord is a really nice guy.
这里离餐厅好近
It's so close to the diner.
如果撞到阿憨 会不会很尴尬啊
Won't it be weird if we run into Han?
我是指不是用车撞的时候
And not with a car?
好了 就是这里
Okay. This is it.
你们好呀
Hello!
靠 我讨厌木偶戏
Oh, no, I hate puppet shows.
依薇 这不行 这是小蛋糕店
Evie, this isn't available, it's a cupcake shop.
除非那两个女孩终于放弃 但那是不可能滴
Unless those two girls finally gave up.
我决定让你俩扩张
I've decided to let you expand.
依薇说服我走出舒适区 做一些不同的事情
Evie convinced me to do things outside my comfort zone.
没错
Yes, I did.
你看看 卡洛琳
How 'bout that, Caroline?
除了我们 她还给别人看了肮脏的黑"地洞"
We're not the only ones she showed a dingy, dark hole to.
收起你的淫秽思想
Get your minds out of the gutter.
她是带我去做热瑜伽
She took me to hot yoga.
他唱颂两下他就吐了
He vomited two "oms" in.
但至少他敢于尝试
But at least he tried.
所以谁知道接下来会试什么呢
So who knows what's next?
我从来没吃过龙虾
Well, I've never had lobster.
阿憨 你确定要这么做吗
Han, are you sure about this?
让我们在这里开甜点吧
You'll let us build our dessert bar here?
我确定我应该马上就会后悔
I'm sure I'll regret it almost immediately.
阿憨 虽然我现在很想抱你
Han, I would hug you right now,
但弊大于利
but the cons outweigh the pros.
这肯定会成为最酷的酒吧
This is gonna be the coolest bar!
我们只需把这玩意弄走
We just have to get rid of that.